Regina Rickson

333 Third Highway, Boise, ID 33333 r. ri ckson ©email, com (111) 222-3333

Senior accounts payable specialist with 11 + years of experience in vendor interactions and payment processes, Able to manage relations with multiple vendors while keeping all accounts in good standing.

Organized bookkeeper whose accurate records prove valuable at tax time and during reconciliation and reviews. Skills include the use of industry-standard software, clear communication, and accounting ability.

Key Skills

- Vendor relations
- Bookkeeping
- Accounting software, including Oracle, NetSuite, and Tipalti
- Written and verbal communication
- Delivering reports

Professional Experience

Senior Accounts Payable Specialist

Boise Business Solutions, Boise, ID I January 2015 - Present

- Process approximately 15,000 invoices per month, covering over 11 million in payments to vendors
- Recommend use of cost-saving measures like early payments and bulk purchases, triggering an average of \$30,000 in vendor discounts per quarter
- Review deliveries and inventory to ensure vendors are meeting obligations
- Reconcile vendor invoices with internal records to identify errors and overpayments, saving \$500,000+ to date
- Deliver weekly and quarterly reports to managers and executives regarding vendor payments, invoice issues, and other account-related matters

Accounts Payable Specialist

Smith Solutions, Bismarck, ND j July 2009 - December 2014

- Reviewed invoice coding for errors, catching an average of 12 per week
- · Kept records on over 40 vendors
- Assisted with end-of-month book dosing
- Resolved several months of backlogged vendor payments through payment plans and open communication
- Researched vendor agreements to find discount opportunities, in one case saving \$12,000 per order

Education

Bachelor of Science in Accounting

Nebraska University, Lincoln, NE, September 2005 - June 2009

Certifications

- Certified Accounts Payable Specialist, Financial Professionals Association, 2019
- ♦ Bookkeeper Certification, Bookkeepers of America, 2020